And I'll make a few more small announcements. News
later,
they want to end the Buddhist class.
The situation we had a while ago, let's see
if, seeing
that, it's the teachers who were Master Sura
and Master Santisteban,
all the water warrior light and
anti-debate teachers, they said that you lose
min e.on, it's good karma if you get angry
with anyone, with anyone, and jets
are cape. I wanted more information, I was saying that this, let's
see what they're talking about,
follow you.
This is a very unusual way of using these
two words. One means object or country, and
the other means to support. But "minaya"
has a special meaning. It means
the person to whom you give
votes. The teacher who uses it and the teacher
who is, so he's using this
meaning here. It means the
person you get angry with and the
person who gets angry. The person who
gets angry and the person with whom they get
angry. "I" is
the person you get angry with, and the
other "Jane" is the person who gets angry. So
he's playing with this
language. If you don't use
binary language, you won't understand. Let's
see what this is. We're going to put it in
an entry.  From the dictionary, Adam,
the waters, it means that, it means that
Lara,
be, means clear,
the campsite means, it's not exactly clear,
so what is it saying
that we are not, it's not very clear in
Santisteban, it's not very clear in Sura,
whether the people they get angry with
are Buddhists or not, it's not clear,
but I'll tell you, if you're going to lose 100
or 1 billion of good karma,
the person you get angry with
should be very wild,
in his opinion. This is
Jayson Capa's opinion: well, come on, if you're going to
lose so many
millions of years or so many billions
of years
in karma, come on, it should be a
wood and save with the person you got
angry with, and more recently, Manolo
said directly,
but it should be,
there are statutes that say
that we already covered, that say that the person
who has the anger has to be not
only a holy body but a
high-level jump, if you're going to lose
1,000 hours of good karma,
100 of good karma, it should be a
coveted powerful one
from the page, page, you know, girl, so that it eats,
reduction of the paste means
extracting  So,
deducing from this,
the person he's angry with should
also be a powerful bodhisattva, not
just a normal judge. To be powerful,
from those
toxic bases that stocks and the four powers,
meaning the person who gets angry,
being powerful, can be powerful, and the one he's
angry with should also be
powerful. That is, acting to make this
powerful combination like a ship
hitting an iceberg.
Jason tells me this here. For the
person who gets angry,
stop the topic. The person who gets angry,
that bodhisattva, is definitely
a partner. Wow,
a person who hasn't seen emptiness
directly. What I mean is, like a
normal person in the sense that they're not
special, they haven't seen it.
It's full in Sanskrit.
If power is moving away, this kind
of anger is
more powerful Buddhists, but they haven't seen
emptiness directly. So we've
learned that if you're a good and safe person,
you necessarily have to have seen it
directly. Even in
that sentence, you can learn something
important in Buddhism. So it can
be someone who has great compassion,
who is dedicated to becoming, I'm going
to help everyone.  The world, and it's not
necessarily that you've already seen the
darkness directly.
It's true that all the people who have seen
emptiness directly are Moix. We're
not saying no
to some very intelligent scientist who does
n't care much about observing the world. They
can understand
that things come from them.
Eisenberg, these people, if you carefully study
some physics, some
atomic scientists have understood this, but they don't
try to save the world with it.
So either way,
if you're a body set, it doesn't
necessarily mean you've
seen emptiness, and if you have seen
emptiness, it's not necessarily true that
you're a boy saver. It's not necessarily
true that if you're a body saver at the
first level of the boys & bass, you've
seen emptiness. Yes, okay, well, you understand. Is there
some way within the 10 bags, is there
some lump within the 10
levels that I haven't seen, even
directly? Not very well, are you
understanding? If you reach nirvana, it
means you've already
perceived what directly... Yes, yes, it
must be like that.
If cancer is in ir, they're going to reach
unity. No,
good answer.
You can be on the police track
and not have  seen
and not having seen the mouth directly if
in the first two paths which is the
long one
within the five paths
the person who gets angry without some doubt has
not seen life directly they are going
to lose so much karma
but what do they think of the object
with which they get angry
he says ready there are two options with
which he supposes to be able to do an area it could
not be an area he could do it as it
may be that not the people with
whom he gets angry
therefore there are three exceptions
there are three solutions in general we
are not talking about the thousand years or
the 100 years and it is still not known
there are three three general options
number one the one
who gets angry is more powerful than the
jealousy of all the one who
gets angry is not so powerful and you
jump like him you can talk to whoever it is
number three is that they like
that passion of powerful ones
which of those three do you suppose
is the one in which the raised tree
loses so much good karma
one of the three loses 100 another of the 3
loses 1000
which one loses 100
the body satuee that gets angry is
the baptized one is less powerful the other
Bodhisattva,
so to explain the
difference, if in power he is not
less powerful, he
loses.
Well, if he could save the one who gets angry, he is
more powerful than the one he gets angry with; he
loses a thousand.
In this case, Jackson uses something
that is evident or obvious, which means
when you say that something is sober, then
when there is a loss of 100 eons, it is
more. It is
not the other way around.
When he says that it is obvious,
and that apparently means that it is
his opinion.
You can say it seems clear, it is clear.
When you say that, which means that you are not
sure. It seems clear that the person who is
eating the cookies from the box is
playing Michael. When you say it seems
clear, he lets people know that it is
your own deduction, and so, in this way,
he warns people that his
opinion is to be careful, without saying that
you are in the opinion of
Kessel. Bodhisattva is less powerful; he
loses a thousand years. If Luisa is not more
powerful, he loses
millions of eons or something like that.
It seems that if you really want to
know how much car you are going to lose,
then you should use writing.
This is when a stop, the machine of being
is foldable, it
tells you, you should.  Checking the
date
is something people have to discover.
When Jackson Capa says there's
no hope,
when he says it's something we have to
discover, he means that
if people later have more access to
the scriptures, they might have more
details. But he says, this is what I know.
If someone later sees more scriptures, if
man has more scriptures, he could
show a better decision. But based
on what we have,
this is what it is when
explaining reduced states
and saving our homeland.
So any bodhisattva who
hurts others is speaking
language and saving them. They get angry in their mind
with someone who isn't yet very accurate
and does some bad actions and hit them
when they go to the planets,
or not
100 million planets, 100
billion planets. He's talking about a
Buddhist who hits others, that is, people
who aren't like us. It's acting. So what does
harm mean? He's
trying to make a
distinction. It's something that gets into a
few programs and gets into a lot of
trouble. The past, the one who gets
into a few problems, is the one who hurts
the general karma of hitting a million.
Of many people,
the other wizard is the one who gets angry with
a Bodhisattva, and that's the one who got angry
with a current Betis. This one has to
put his armor back on.
This is important when we put
Stansted there were more. I'm going to try to finish
today
when Moody Science
gets angry in his heart with another boy
save, but he doesn't say anything to him, he doesn't say
anything at all. He's just angry in his heart with
the bones,
that's all.
Any moments of not playing,
the eons that happen, sorry, those will be
the eons that they will have to put
their armor back on. So we want to
know what it means when it
says that he has to put
his armor back on again. The Bodhisattva pigs who
hit so
many people in billions
of worlds don't get hurt that much, but a
visa. But one says that he gets angry for a
second with others, sometimes they lose
a lot of time. They have to spend a
neon for each moment of anger
putting on their armor. What does it mean?
Oh my god, it's going to get so out of hand.
The whole topic
says it's apparent. What does that mean? That it's
your own opinion. It's apparent that the
person you get angry with
is  A Buddhist
who hasn't yet received confirmation is
like when I was a little kid
in the Christian church. When you turn
16, when you're a baby, you're baptized and
become a Christian. You don't have to do
anything, you just cry.
But later, you have to
study the preferences of the sect
in the ceremonies and the peace exam. The
ceremony is called confirmation;
it's like certifying that you're a
true Christian. You're old enough
to understand the ideas.
We have confirmation in Buddhism too; it's called long. It has
its center in karma
here,
and without a doubt, it sees you and tells you, I do
n't know, what day in December, December
2024, you had to become a Buddha. You already have
enough good karma, which is good. It can
see you,
and it's funny because they used to only do it by
putting their foot on your head.
But we haven't been like that, and
they look at your karma and the date
of 2024. They can give you a date. Some
people aren't good enough
yet to have that confirmation,
and when you don't follow through, it's a bit
uncertain.
Maybe they'll emphasize doing something important
today or next year. There's something that
the person you
're with says...  Angry is not confirmed yet
but the visa they feel anger sorry sorry let's
see the body save with which you get
angry
the bodhisattva with which you get angry
is confirmed but the wizard Vazquez
gets angry is not confirmed
and then goes to appointments another to test it let's see
excuse this of ours from the water
there was save that is not confirmed
yet
gets angry with men behind that if he is
there they already have their illumination date
confirmed
if they get angry
sky and saturate that is not confirmed
although you don't have confirmation yet
a man comes down who already has his
confirmation they will have to do a
neon again armor
is getting interesting what does that
mean the mature ones we don't
know I'm
not going to say
what it means without him
already kills
without him
means the same the second syllable
this not under flame is it is cinema and cinema
means finally
so you ask
your assistants for orange juice in
the morning and it comes after
noon and they say yes
finally at last that didn't
happen that didn't happen to me it's just
an example I already
have it like 10 seconds later
I have the whole glove
Ginés means
ay  What does it mean? They're going to have to start over.
Ginés means to have to
put the armor back on. What does that mean?
Yes, a Bodhisattva
was in the final steps of the first
of the five paths. They are in
the final stages of the first
of the five paths and are about to reach
the second. What happens in the second? The
first one has a bridge. It's even in
your life that you become
spiritual.
Disasters are very good.
Let's talk about health. Scales. Lachila.
The first one: you have
a big problem in your life. You
become spiritual. Your mother dies in your
arms. Your brother shoots himself. And then
suddenly you're like, "No way!
Life is different from how I imagined it. It's not
just rock and roll."
It's the first path of the tractor. The
second path: In
the second one, someone explains the
feather to you. When you get far enough in the
second path, you can no longer go anywhere
lower. So don't complain.
When I explained the feathers, there's a
French guy in Singapore who asks, "
Why do you always teach about
the feather? Why do you always teach about the feather?" I tell him, "
Well, you're
keeping yourself out of hell." Okay,
sometimes the lamas,
maybe
ready for the path,
but he got angry with another one.
Powell's visa also means how to graduate,
not just projecting your
global consciousness, and then they'll move on to the second
level,
but he got angry with a Bodhisattva Schattmann who
already had his date arranged. Karabuda
Age Jets, a boss, is taking it out of
different sutras to give a
clear answer. It's difficult, but it's
clear: if you give up because it's difficult, I ca
n't help you. You shouldn't come to
these classes. You want something easy? Go somewhere else. It's
difficult, but it's true.
That other Bodhisattva has to be one of
the Buddhas or some lama. They already made his
day. What can the future
tell us? He means a moment
of anger. You don't want to go alone like a
second-rate person. It has to be
like a few hours or something like that, like
you really hate it for a couple of hours. It
has to be a sustained anger,
like so many moments of sustained anger
that you have, but like a strong anger
that you don't let go of for many hours.
They won't be able to move
to the second level for all that amount
of eons. Okay, do you understand? Someone
isn't facing it like, "
If Maicon, if not..."  It can destroy more
seeds. How come it doesn't? Well,
you can destroy the good ones. This is a
good answer because he doesn't
destroy his good seeds, he only
delays them for a certain time. With every
certain amount of time, he
delays his progress, and he will probably
never know why.
He won't know why for a long time he wo
n't be able to climb and go up.
Only after a long time will
he have to keep practicing the
same old things,
reach the point where he thought he was going to
reach the
second path next week, but he gets angry
over a gram of salt, and then he
only delays his journey by 100
million years.
That means he's going to have to
go back again. It was going to be 100
million years again, another 100
million years. Another
lioness. He has to start all over again. It's
like going back to the beginning again,
walking a million miles. He gets angry
for five minutes,
they get a helicopter back to the
beginning, and he starts again. In fact, it's
worse than that. Do you understand? That's what it
means to destroy your karma.
Here, this is one of the true ones.
In some cases, you have to go back to the...  The
beginning
is also we
're almost at the end, we're almost done when
I have 13 minutes of that thick layer.
Master Santiago says that the Buddha
said
that if you get angry with a Moody's Water who
has been very generous in his life,
then for every instant of
anger, hatred towards them, that's why, just like he has
ones, you should stay in the
hells. Now the game has changed,
now and the sinkhole is satisfied, he
keeps bringing out more things about it, he's very, very
capable. I'm
going to give you the translations, spend some
time with them, you're going to discover things and
deeper things. That's the style of
Jets or Layer, and done, Layer not finished.
So they talk, they destroy the restaurant,
to return to the first path and that it takes
a million eleven.
Now he's talking about the restaurant of the
hells, not to return to the first
path.
Yes, of course, it does extract a lot of good
field, but also
if a person who doesn't yet have the
confirmation date of their age gets angry
with one who does,
having to go back to the beginning is just as
bad as going back to clean, which is
hell.
So what am I going to start with? In
fact, you can say both go to
hell
and we start again.
That price is
now going to go to others, another is called
the whole case in the universe,
everything in the universe explodes into dust, everything is
pulverized with your wisdom, with
understanding of all that is, its
transcendence,
its tradition.
There is a bad karma called giving
up on the soul's dharma, like
giving up on continuing to study, giving up
on giving more
if it's not like I decided they scam and all that
dharma stuff is silly, it's stupid,
stupid because someone told me that
because if you always have an excuse like that, like I
already thought that I don't like this group
that usually focus very badly on what is
the karma of that,
what is the karma of that,
and
if it's also your mind, then you change your mind
and for seven years
with parties,
that negative karma three times a day, what do I say,
doubt your others,
this, they are not capable, another could, said that
your abandonment is the weapon, says I don't want any
more weapons, not anymore,
and then for seven years
you change your mind and you say I wasn't wrong, I'm sorry,
and for seven years
every day, every day in the morning, in
the late afternoon, and later
you confess I made a mistake, what happened,
you can  Cleanse the karma, and you can cleanse
that karma,
but those people can't
reach
the number one state called Santi
Patience. They can't reach that for 10
million years, in Milan years.
This mastery in Santi and in patience, you don't have to
be an animal, no attention,
be a hungry spirit.
That's the level within the level of the
form you have to reach.
There are certain bad things you can do, I
lost drugs, very hard. The four
powers, you can cleanse them, you don't have to
go to anyone's hell.
But there's a second result, which is a
10 million year delay that we're not going
to hear
explained from the pen. Easy when
Vision Michael explains the pen that it's going to
be backward and you're going to return to the fourth
when it's over. No, no, if it really happened, it
happened this week.
I have to regulate it. I have it. The good
job, fool, the one you missed. No
way.
So Jett are capable, it shouldn't matter.
Confessing, it
shouldn't matter. Being the four powers,
I don't know why,
because they didn't make you go to hell
to fix the delay. He says no, you can't
fix it.
No matter how many times I confess, you can't
fix it. You'll
always be in
the bathroom when you call her, I
explained the feathers,
all these letters, you'll always come back
when you're already asking for money again,
if we have other projects too,
what's going to start